usa.edu 2001-02-19

# Internet Privacy Policy

### Internet Privacy Policy

The University utilizes email links located on each page and on the Directory page to allow you to contact us directly with any questions or comments you may have. We read every message sent in and try to reply promptly to every one. This information is used to respond directly to your questions or comments. We may also use your comments to improve the site and program. 

Any personal information disclosed in an email note, address, phone number, etc. is used only for the purposes you have requested. Information will be entered into a University database for purposes of following-up on your request. This information is utilized by authorized University personnel only and is not disclosed to third parties. 

If you use our secure online server to register for a continuing education class, we ask that you submit the minimal amount of information needed to process your request. 

Students are encouraged to request an update concerning any personal information stored, so that our records will be complete and accurate. This information is not disclosed to any third parties. 

The University may use email address information submitted by you, to alert students of new course offerings or of other news related to University programs. 
### Internet Privacy Policy

The University utilizes email links located on each page and on the Directory page to allow you to contact us directly with any questions or comments you may have. We read every message sent in and try to reply promptly to every one. This information is used to respond directly to your questions or comments. We may also use your comments to improve the site and program. 

Any personal information disclosed in an email note, address, phone number, etc. is used only for the purposes you have requested. Information will be entered into a University database for purposes of following-up on your request. This information is utilized by authorized University personnel only and is not disclosed to third parties. 

If you use our secure online server to register for a continuing education class, we ask that you submit the minimal amount of information needed to process your request. 

Students are encouraged to request an update concerning any personal information stored, so that our records will be complete and accurate. This information is not disclosed to any third parties. 

The University may use email address information submitted by you, to alert students of new course offerings or of other news related to University programs.
